<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Chaos on Art of Dmitry Brushray</title>
    <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/tags/chaos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chaos on Art of Dmitry Brushray</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 17:18:38 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://artbrushray.github.io/tags/chaos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Iron Butchers preparations for a battle, plus a story.</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/preparations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 17:18:38 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/preparations/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;#39;ve seen plenty of art and video how space marines are served and prepared for a battle. All these are about loyal astartes. Correct me, but I&amp;#39;ve never seen an art where renegades or chaos marines are served. It may be some of them no need such procedure as they fused with their armor. But I think there are warbands and space marines which are less corrupted by chaos and still needed this service every once in a while. So we thought it would be interesting to imagine how ironclading could look like for ChSM. And today I&amp;#39;m happy to show you the result along with the small description below. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storm of Iron</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/stormofiron/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 18:34:16 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/stormofiron/</guid>
      <description>Storm of Iron</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vhorrax, Iron Warriors Warsmith remastered</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/vorraxv2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 15:03:14 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/vorraxv2/</guid>
      <description>Hey everybody! This work is pretty special, a bit more that a year ago form this art I started my collaboration with Iron Butchers warband: https://www.instagram.com/enter.the.butcher/ Back then I did the first version of this art: https://www.artstation.com/artwork/2qn9qg Since then I&amp;rsquo;ve painted a lot of great art for the Iron Butchers. I learned a lot and improved. Now I thought the time has come to revamp the art. I hope you like the new version of Vhorrax, Iron Warriors Warsmith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Mechanicum creation</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/megatherion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 15:00:14 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/megatherion/</guid>
      <description>In collaboration with https://www.instagram.com/enter.the.butcher/ Iron Butchers I&amp;rsquo;ve painted a birth of the monstrous engine created by the Dark Mechanicum. Here is a brief description abouth the artwork:
Warsmith Vhorrax Immanibus, leader of the Iron Butchers, contemplates the birth of the monstrous daemon engine called &amp;ldquo;the Megatherion&amp;rdquo;.
Crafted by the combined efforts of the Dark Mechanicum and the Warband&amp;rsquo;s Warpsmiths, the Megatherion is a knight-sized monstrosity inhabited by not one, but dozens of daemons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rot and Iron</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/rotiron/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 22:47:14 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/rotiron/</guid>
      <description>Small story which the art illustrates:
His wasn&amp;rsquo;t supposed to happen for the Blightstars to now be locked in a small-scale conflict with their former allies, the Rust Corps. All from a single, stray shell. The Blightstars, in their attempt to soften the Imperial forces, had deployed plagueburst crawlers to fire artillery upon the loyalist lines. How could they have known that the manic beast known as Ferrinox was running rampant on the front lines or that one of the many shots fired from their mortars would strike upon his position?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The bearer of the beak&#39;s words</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/raptor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 22:46:14 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/raptor/</guid>
      <description>The champion is one of the bearers of the beak&amp;rsquo;s words. He is honoured and respected by his brethren. The warband worship a greater daemon with no parts of the four dark gods. They are calling the greater daemon a god, and gain minor boons, along with mutations from it.
The leader of the warband is the head priest, Arkus Cain. Once a word-bearer, now hunted and exiled from the legion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Havok Smith Trelok Olethros</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/havoksmith/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 22:45:14 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/havoksmith/</guid>
      <description>Hey everybody! This big bastard is Havok Smith Trelok Olethros the warlord of the Rust Corps Iron warrior warband. He replaced his arm with a chain cannon after losing in a fight with a Dark Angels Ravenwing captain. Most importantly he is completely and totally insane.
The Iron Warriors were the IV Legion of the twenty original Space Marine Legions. Their Primarch is Perturabo. They were one of the nine legions which betrayed the Emperor during the Horus Heresy, becoming Chaos Space Marines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black legion space marine</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/blacklegion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 20:45:14 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/blacklegion/</guid>
      <description>Another Chaos space marine fan art.
He is Black Legion. His lore has had him fight various greater demons in the warp.
Like my work? Feel free to contact me ✉ for your personalized piece of art anytime!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warsmith Vorrax v1</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/vorraxv1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 18:45:14 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/vorraxv1/</guid>
      <description>This guy is an Iron Warrior Warsmith of one imaginary Chaos Warband. He is wearing a terminator cataphractii armor, he is devoted to Khorne. He is really into dark and heretic technologies and equipped with a big thunder hammer in his right hand, in the left hand he got a heavy flamer.
Like my work? Feel free to contact me ✉ for your personalized piece of art anytime!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
