<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Emperor on Art of Dmitry Brushray</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/the-emperor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Emperor on Art of Dmitry Brushray</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 17:24:35 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/the-emperor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>the Emperor of mankind, fan art by Dmitry Brushray</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/theemperor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 17:24:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/theemperor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone! Today I want to show you something really special.
Ever since I started painting Warhammer fan art for many reasons I hadn&amp;rsquo;t been dared to think of approaching this potent figure, the Emperor of mankind. Besides required strong artistic skills one important reason was that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t see any good idea or a context to show him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/2024/The_Emperor_by_brushray.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;The Emperor of Mankind, art by Dmitry Brushray&#34;  /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then it has come pretty sudden, I guess it could be called an inspiration. First I realised his might could be shown only in comparison with some other objects or characters. I wanted to add astartes to his side but then I thought their size and anatomy indistinct too so instead I decided to add people. Small and puny as they are they became a great contrast to his scale, and it benefited for the further idea progress.
At once a context stuck to the idea: he reveals his nature to these two poor souls. Librarians let them be, an old man and a young woman. The old man just can&amp;rsquo;t stand the Emperor side. The woman is a mild psyker so she is more sensitive. He begs her to turn her gaze down but she is ecstatic. She feels the Emperor&amp;rsquo;s might is unbearable and yet she can&amp;rsquo;t not to watch.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
