<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Art of Dmitry Brushray</title>
    <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Art of Dmitry Brushray</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 22:47:06 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Female torso quick paintings</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/female_torso_by_brushray/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 22:47:06 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/female_torso_by_brushray/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Culsu, a World Eater Chaos Lord second-in-command of the Iron Butchers Warband</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/culsu2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 23:57:31 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/culsu2/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone! This is another revamp of one of my work. The first art of this character was painted something about a year ago for the Iron Butchers warband: https://www.instagram.com/enter.the.butcher/ Here is the link to the post with the first version of Culsu: https://www.artstation.com/artwork/6bXRxV
Then there had been some progress in my vision and work process and we decided to make another art ot the character. So this post is the result: a character with helmet and without, plus some stages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My charcoal practice of portraits</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/portraits2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 21:51:59 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/portraits2/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone! Some more charcoal practice here. I had another busy month, mostly have been working doing print design which is infinitely more boring then drawing. Spare time I was spending on traditional media. My goal is to master charcoal. It&amp;rsquo;s intermediate material to the oil paint and it has some of oil&amp;rsquo;s features. Simple and expressive it perfectly fits for studying forms and value.
I know you might have been waiting for some digital stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hands drawing practice</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/hands1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 21:26:44 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/hands1/</guid>
      <description>I keep practicing with charcoal. I&amp;rsquo;m gradually trying to move from still life to anatomy starting with hands and feets. Also have a lot to do to improve the charcoal usage itself and master the material.
#brushray #artbrushray #artist #art #painting #artcommissions #buyart #art #tradtitional #charcoal #hands #anatomy #forart
Like my work? Feel free to contact me ✉ for your personalized piece of art anytime!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
