<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Art of Dmitry Brushray</title>
    <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Art of Dmitry Brushray</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 17:24:35 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>the Emperor of mankind, fan art by Dmitry Brushray</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/theemperor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 17:24:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/theemperor/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone! Today I want to show you something really special. Ever since I started painting Warhammer fan art for many reasons I hadn&amp;rsquo;t been dared to think of approaching this potent figure, the Emperor of mankind. Besides required strong artistic skills one important reason was that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t see any good idea or a context to show him.
Then it has come pretty sudden, I guess it could be called an inspiration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revamp of the ugliest fan art I ever painted, Necron Lord</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/lord_necron/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 17:15:04 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/lord_necron/</guid>
      <description>Recently I picked this idea of repainting my old art. It helps to spot some problems and estimate my current progress. After making few revamps I decided to pick I guess one of my biggest fails. Every time I see the initial art I had made, it reminds me horrors of the warp. I still don&amp;rsquo;t know how it happened, after all I wasn&amp;rsquo;t that bad at that time but with this fan art something went really wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November 23 Dmitry Brushray Art mix</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/nov23mix/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 22:24:38 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/nov23mix/</guid>
      <description>Mix of my artworks November 2023.
I keep painting chaos space marines. This guy has pretty unusual and bright colour scheme. He&amp;rsquo;s a chaos champion for a warband called the Reproached Hollows, He&amp;rsquo;s only known as &amp;ldquo;The Cyclopes&amp;rdquo; Special thanks to Littlerevy and her miniature reference: https://instagram.com/littlerevy?igshid=MzRlODBiNWFlZA==
Roman warrior, short personal work, a painting study
In this personal work called &amp;ldquo;Lady Victory&amp;rdquo; I was inspired by knights and medieval, fantasy vibes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Daemonastrolabium of the Iron Maw</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/compass/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 17:11:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/compass/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone! Today is a special artwork on Warhammer40k here. We keep expanding lore of the Iron Butchers warband: Make sure to check their instagram: https://www.instagram.com/enter.the.butcher/
If you may remember I painted a star ship for this warband, the Iron Maw, on which they crusade the Galaxy: https://www.artstation.com/artwork/g00LWe This artwork shows a pretty special part of this ship called The Daemonastrolabium. Basically it&amp;rsquo;s a huge compass which navigates the warp.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
