<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Warhammer40k on Art of Dmitry Brushray</title>
    <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/tags/warhammer40k/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Warhammer40k on Art of Dmitry Brushray</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 17:18:38 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://artbrushray.github.io/tags/warhammer40k/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Iron Butchers preparations for a battle, plus a story.</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/preparations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 17:18:38 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/preparations/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;#39;ve seen plenty of art and video how space marines are served and prepared for a battle. All these are about loyal astartes. Correct me, but I&amp;#39;ve never seen an art where renegades or chaos marines are served. It may be some of them no need such procedure as they fused with their armor. But I think there are warbands and space marines which are less corrupted by chaos and still needed this service every once in a while. So we thought it would be interesting to imagine how ironclading could look like for ChSM. And today I&amp;#39;m happy to show you the result along with the small description below. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storm of Iron</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/stormofiron/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 18:34:16 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/stormofiron/</guid>
      <description>Storm of Iron</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vhorrax, Iron Warriors Warsmith remastered</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/vorraxv2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 15:03:14 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/vorraxv2/</guid>
      <description>Hey everybody! This work is pretty special, a bit more that a year ago form this art I started my collaboration with Iron Butchers warband: https://www.instagram.com/enter.the.butcher/ Back then I did the first version of this art: https://www.artstation.com/artwork/2qn9qg Since then I&amp;rsquo;ve painted a lot of great art for the Iron Butchers. I learned a lot and improved. Now I thought the time has come to revamp the art. I hope you like the new version of Vhorrax, Iron Warriors Warsmith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Mechanicum creation</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/megatherion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 15:00:14 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/megatherion/</guid>
      <description>In collaboration with https://www.instagram.com/enter.the.butcher/ Iron Butchers I&amp;rsquo;ve painted a birth of the monstrous engine created by the Dark Mechanicum. Here is a brief description abouth the artwork:
Warsmith Vhorrax Immanibus, leader of the Iron Butchers, contemplates the birth of the monstrous daemon engine called &amp;ldquo;the Megatherion&amp;rdquo;.
Crafted by the combined efforts of the Dark Mechanicum and the Warband&amp;rsquo;s Warpsmiths, the Megatherion is a knight-sized monstrosity inhabited by not one, but dozens of daemons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
