<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Warhammer40k on Art of Dmitry Brushray</title>
    <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/tags/warhammer40k/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Warhammer40k on Art of Dmitry Brushray</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 18:21:55 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://artbrushray.github.io/tags/warhammer40k/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>From the void the Iron Maw comes</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/ibship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 18:21:55 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/ibship/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone! Fresh art for Iron Butchers https://www.instagram.com/enter.the.butcher/ This time it&amp;rsquo;s a ship the warband uses to crusade the galaxy. Plus here is a bit of story content from Iron Butchers public. Please, enjoy.
Captain Heuldrasia was carried on the Command Bridge by her personal servitor. She was cradled in its arms like a baby in the mother&amp;rsquo;s chest. The servitor laid the Captain&amp;rsquo;s mangled body in the Command Throne, and rapidly connected to the ship&amp;rsquo;s systems, allowing her mind to fuse, once more, with the ship&amp;rsquo;s Machine Spirit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brother Samial Venritus of Dark Angels </title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/semial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 01:15:15 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/semial/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iron Butchers preparations for a battle, plus a story.</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/preparations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 17:18:38 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/preparations/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;#39;ve seen plenty of art and video how space marines are served and prepared for a battle. All these are about loyal astartes. Correct me, but I&amp;#39;ve never seen an art where renegades or chaos marines are served. It may be some of them no need such procedure as they fused with their armor. But I think there are warbands and space marines which are less corrupted by chaos and still needed this service every once in a while. So we thought it would be interesting to imagine how ironclading could look like for ChSM. And today I&amp;#39;m happy to show you the result along with the small description below. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storm of Iron</title>
      <link>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/stormofiron/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 18:34:16 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artbrushray.github.io/posts/stormofiron/</guid>
      <description>Storm of Iron</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
